Courage runs deep
Hunter Killer is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Donovan Marsh.
Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d'état is taking place in Russia, so
he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.
Captain Joe Glass, played by Gerard Butler.
CJCS Charles Donnegan, played by Gary Oldman.
Bill Beaman, played by Toby Stephens.
RA John Fisk, played by Common.
Jane Norquist, played by Linda Cardellini.
Cob Wallach, played by David Gyasi.
Hunter Killer is a 2018 American action thriller film
starring Gerard Butler and Gary Oldman.
Based on the 2012 novel Firing Point by Don Keith and George Wallace, the film follows a submarine crew and
a group of United States Navy SEALs who rescue the captured Russian President from a coup.
Directed by Donovan Marsh and written by Arne Schmidt and Jamie Moss, it features Michael Nyqvist (in his
penultimate film role), Common, Linda Cardellini and Toby Stephens in supporting roles.
Hunter Killer was released in the United States on
October 26, 2018, by Summit Premiere.
The film bombed at the box-office and received mixed reviews from critics,
who saw it as "an undemanding, by-the-numbers actioner".
The film explores themes of sniper, washington dc,
usa, submarine, pentagon, u.s. navy.
The tone is intense.